hello so today uh i would like to
discuss one one stock which is uh
va tech we're back uh
this one stock uh
is in merida and
the reason for for looking at this
company is uh considering we have
huge uh bull run in small cap so still
i want to
add some which are which which has not
with the the sectors which have not
moved much so
in this case i've taken this va tech web
bug which is in water treatment uh water
treatment field and this is still at a
reasonable valuation as per me so market
cap to sales is still below one
current price is around 340 is around uh
this this company is in water treatment
field uh it includes design supply
installation construction and
for management of drinking water
wastewater treatment industrial water
treatment and desolation and we know in
india there's a lot of problem for
industrial water treatment wastewater
treatment even for drinking water
so and
recently i think in last one year we
have seen
government
uh boosting or putting a lot of effort
for
water
uh drinking water infrastructure to to
the homes even in rural rural areas so
this uh this talk uh came into the
picture it it hasn't moved much as for
me so it was around okay 200 levels and
then yeah it's around 340 300 level so
uh it's a it's a reasonable evolution
debt to equity is 0.25 which is which is
quite good uh and
this this company is regularly
winning orders you see some
1230 correlation order
they have quite an increase in pat
so yeah they they are they are uh
and we we need this wastewater treatment
i think uh there are a lot of big mncs
also in this in this area but this
company is uh
executing well and
uh
you see this they
have shown and their continuously
showing increased orders and
they are they are not only in india they
are in different parts of the world uh
so they are in major orders are they
getting from middle east africa india
switzerland and romania so
they have 90 process beatens as well so
this company looks really good to me
as of now
so slowly uh
we can start
yeah if you like the company you can
start adding and uh
let's see maybe one or two year and
we'll see how this company executes
so they have different kinds of
options and what all industries they
cater to so they cater to oil and gas
power plants steel and yeah
so this this uh this is looking good uh
as for me uh so just a uh
standard disclaimer please consult your
financial advisor i'm not arrested be
registered uh investment advisor
also second point which i always mention
in all of my uh
videos uh please diversify don't put say
10 or 15 percent in one stock my
recommendation is start with uh start
with say suppose two or three percent
and then slowly increase to five percent
if you if you really like the story if
you really like the thesis
uh so overall this company is good uh
and we can start adding
that's it
thanks for your time
bye